Curtis Gibson

10 Tinworth Street, Flat 105G, London, SE11 5AL

Mobile Number: 07749859610

Email Address: curtisgib@hotmail.co.uk

Personal Profile

An enthusiastic, ambitious and current student at City, University of London studying Computer Science under the Professional Pathway scheme. Currently with a three year placement at Firstco, my objective is to leave my mark with something people will remember, to build a career with intentions to change the industry. Being a computer science student, I have developed problem solving skills as well as being able to multi-task with different ongoing projects.

Education

September 2016 - June 2019	City, University of London	BSc Computer Science
Year 1	First	
Year 2	Pending	

Year 2 Pending
Year 3 Pending
Year 4 Pending

September 2014 - June 2016 Portadown College A-Level & Equivalent

Level 3 Subsidiary Diploma in IT Distinction*

Information Technology B
Moving Image Arts B
Technology & Design C

September 2012 - June 2014 Portadown College GCSE

10 GCSE's Grades A* to C including English, Maths & A* in ICT

Technical Skills

As a second year undergraduate, I have developed technical knowledge in the following areas:

- Java Programming (Intermediate)
- Siemens WinCC Open Architecture (Intermediate)
- Microsoft Office Package Word, Excel & PowerPoint (Advanced)
- Apple Mac OSX (Advanced)
- Microsoft OS (Advanced)

I have the determination to succeed and develop new and necessary skills required for this role.

Transferrable Skills

Prioritisation & Time Management - Developed through my part time managerial job where I had to run a team of employees in a busy environment, ensuring all customer orders and repairs were carried out swiftly and to the customer's satisfaction.

Communication/Fast Paced - Whilst working in Firstco, I have developed this skill greatly. By communicating with clients, suppliers and industry partners, this has grown my confidence in being able to handle difficult situations without support. No matter what, I always pride myself in ensuring the client is always satisfied, regardless of the situation.

Team Player & Using Initiative - I have continually grown in leadership within various roles, building relationships with employees and clients and being able to work as part of a well organised team. With working in a team I have improved my work load efficiency and constructive use of time. I also know how to use my own initiative when it comes to dealing with customers as a manager or team player. Being able to solve a situation or problem without a higher member of staff can be a difficult task, however I have built this skill whilst in my manager position at Phone Hub.

Employment History

Firstco June 2017 - Present Student Engineer

Currently undertaking a three year placement as a student engineer. My roles include developing SCADA systems, within projects such as a Tunnel Control System for Heathrow Express and a new baggage system for Heathrow Airport. I have worked within both a small and large team, therefore communication is key to succeed. I have developed my programming skills, communication and team working within my placement so far.

Urban Media February 2016 - Present Photographer/Videographer

As a dedicated and hard working individual, I decided to start up my own small business; Urban Media, producing wedding and promotional videos for clients. Developing a start-up has shown my commitment, hard work and creative skills that are required to run a business; although still in its early stages the venture is a somewhat success, still generating interest by clients.

Phone Hub September 2014 - August 2016 Part Time Manager

Initially hired as a sales/repair assistant which not only developed my 'people skills' but also my technological ability to identify the source of problems and repair them. I was later appointed as a graphic designer which allowed me to brand the business, create and maintain the website, and also design the leaflets. Both roles required initiative and leadership skills when deciding and repairing any problems. My promotion to Summer Manager required me to run the daily workings of the shop, set weekly targets and also communicate effectively with staff and customers which advanced my leadership skills but also my ability to work in a team.

BNL Productions March 2013 - August 2016 Freelance Camera Operator

Working for BNL Productions for over three years has developed and instilled in me invaluable skills. These have been gained through my various roles, such as a camera operator & video editor. Producing a unique project for a client requires commitment, creativity and high attention to detail; all of which were demonstrated throughout my position. In addition to this, freelance work gave me the opportunity to produce photography and videography for all different occasions, meaning I required high versatility. Adapting my skills to cater for an array of styles, customers and events meant my creative side flourished whilst my technical use of the equipment and software constantly improved. Not only this, but throughout my time here my communication and listening skills were greatly advanced due to dealing with clients, handling complaints and keeping in touch throughout the project.

Projects and Achievements

Vice President - City Tech Society (Sep 2016 - Present)

As Vice President of City Tech Society, I organise various events throughout the year from weekly workshops to our annual hackathon, HackCity. During 2016-17, I received over £8000 in sponsorship funds for HackCity by partnering with various companies in London. This event was attended by over 100 students and we aim to build upon this each year.

Third place & Overall audience's favourite idea at CitySpark Marketplace Final (December 2016) Having entered the CitySpark business competition during my first year at City, University of London, we

were shortlisted to the Christmas Marketplace Final. During the final we engaged with investors and judges who then voted for their favourite and the best business ideas. Our business idea won 3rd place, and also won the audience's favourite idea on the night.

Vice President - City Tech Society (Sep 2016 - Present)

As Vice President of City Tech Society, I organise various events throughout the year from weekly workshops to our annual hackathon, HackCity. During 2016-17, I received over £8000 in sponsorship funds for HackCity from various companies in London. This event was attended by over 100 students and we aim to build upon this each year.

References

Available on request